{
    "id": "a09cafaafc9c4ba49c31ae2c1a41cb3a",
    "title": "Can, May, And Could",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. be on holiday, but I’m not sure.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4de526b5899e4e6cb01ac5941a2efafe"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………….. be right, but I would still like to check.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f405354ca8cd4afd8770e833503487b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. you turn down the volume, please?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9885a4c940d3440b94aab41ae87d8793"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………… go when you have finished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9382039682e5420cb3977c18046e9a4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………….. ask whatever questions you have.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "37ba5f1f74e94008a90984e3ddc2520b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… smoke in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "cannot",
                "should not",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "c6224643520b4c2b8ccad14f7a46f0d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "From his accent, he ………………….. be from Toronto.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e04076ead2a4e2f8443ad5e26e33c09"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Who can it be?’ ‘It ……………….. the postman.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may not",
                "cannot",
                "must not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ba22f7e6ebfe4fbd96e1aa5369bee4b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather ……………… be hotter tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f203209de10e4b9fb1c0f5c68635538c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. you dance?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee0f48ea8de34aef869fe64c9fd9f373"
        }
    ]
}